A Finding Aid to the Christine Burgin Gallery Records, 1980-2016, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1980-2016; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 8.4 Linear feet Boxes 2-10; 35.75 Gigabytes ER01-ER29
  - Saret, Alan, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1987-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Printed Material, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Shaver, Richard, 2002-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER23
  - Shaver, Richard, Digital Images, 2002; Archival Resource Key; 0.006 Gigabytes 3 computer files (Folder ER23)
  - Silverthorne, Jeanne, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Biography, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Consignments and Loans, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Printed and Photographic Material, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Rope (1991), Exhibition at Fernando Alcolea Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Writings by Silverthorne about "The Model", circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Michael, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Baby Ikki at the Museum Book, 2009-2015; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER24
    - Baby Ikki at the Museum, Digital Images, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.079 Gigabytes 38 computer files (Folder ER24)
    - Consignments and Loans, 2002-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Ellen de Bruijne Projects, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Images of Drawings, Digital, 2003-2007; Archival Resource Key; 7.43 Gigabytes 262 computer files (Folder ER25)
    - Inventory and Storage, 2011-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Lenticular Picture Lightbox, 2005-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER26
    - Lenticular Picture Lightbox, Digital Images, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.035 Gigabytes 2 computer files (Folder ER26)
    - Open House Project, Images and Video, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 3.95 Gigabytes 12 computer files (Folder ER27)
    - Portfolio of Works, Digital Videos, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 6.56 Gigabytes 3 computer files (Folder ER28)
    - Press Package, 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Printed Material, 1997-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Sears Class Portraits Photograph Edition, 2007-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Swennen, Walter, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Tomaselli, Fred, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Tuerlinckx, Jöelle, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Turrell, James, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - van Bonin, Cosima, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - van de Pavert, Jan, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Vercruysse, Jan, 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Vercruysse, Jan, 1987-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Verhoeven, Gert, 2000-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Verhoeven, Gert, The Blob, 2001; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Wall, Jeff, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Wegman, William, Digital Images, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.384 Gigabytes 6 computer files (Folder ER29)
  - Welling, James, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - West, Franz, 1989-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Wilke, Hannah, circa 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Exhibition Files, 1986-2015; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 5 Linear feet Boxes 10-15; 16.53 Gigabytes ER30-ER43
  Exhibition files date from 1986-2015 and document the dozens of exhibitions at the gallery during their two periods of operation, 1986-1992 and 1999-2007. Files include correspondence, price lists, sales records, expenses, installation documentation, concept and planning documentation, photographic material, press releases, artist biographies, exhibition announcements, and clippings. This series also contains material in born-digital form, including images of artwork and installations, document files, as well as audiovisual recordings.
  - John Cage (1986), 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Jake Berthot, Ross Bleckner, Harvey Quaytman, Joan Snyder (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Sam Messer: Sculpture (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Dan Graham, Rodney Graham, Robert Smithson, Jeff Wall (1987), 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Chris Burden: All the Submarines of the United States of America (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
  - Alan Saret (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Hermann Pitz (1987), 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Works on Paper: Gerhard Richter, Richard Serra, Cy Twombly (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Fariba Hajamadi (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Fariba Hajamadi, Gerhard Merz, James Welling (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Gilbert & George, Donald Judd, Tony Tasset (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Fariba Hajamadi (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - James Welling (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Group Exhibition (1988), 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Rodney Graham: Standard Edition (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - "The Lamp of Memory," Photographs, 1848-1880 (1988), 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Seeing is Believing (1989), 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Chris Burden: Devil Drawings (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Jessica Diamond, Mike Kelley, Al Ruppersberg (1989), 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Rodney Graham, Fariba Hajamadi, Christina Iglesias, John Murphy (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Jeanne Silverthorne (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - John Cade, Alan Saret, Richard Tuttle (1990), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Jan Vercruysse (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Richard Nonas (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Allen Ruppersberg (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Ian Hamilton Finlay (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Ian Hamilton Finlay: Eight Proposals (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Fariba Hajamadi (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Rodney Graham (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Jürgen Meyer (1991), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles, 1970-75 (1991), 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
  - Fariba Hajamadi (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Jan Vercruysse: Books and Prints (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Buckminster Fuller (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Recent Additions by Gallery Artists (1991), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - John Murphy (1991), 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22-24)
  - Letters (1991), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Paul Etienne Lincoln: "In Tribute to Madame de Pompadour and the Court of Louis XV" (1991), 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Allen Ruppersberg: Personal Art (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - David Deutsch (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Ernst Caramelle (1992), 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Rodney Graham, Sherrie Levine, James Welling (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Jürgen Meyer, Jessica Stockholder, Franz West (1992), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Lili Dujourie, Jeanne Silverthorne, Pia Stadtbäumer, Rachel Whiteread (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Rodney Graham: Works, 1938-1998 (1999), 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Günther Förd: Zlijn (2000), 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Paul Etienne Lincoln: The World and Its Inhabitants (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Max Neuhaus: Image from Eight Vectors, 1953-2000 (2000), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12-13)
  - Allen Ruppersberg: "Honey I rearranged the Collection..." (2000), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Fred Tomaselli and Rick Moody: Phrase Book and Recommended Reading (2000), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
  - Gert Verhoeven: Dramatis Personae (2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Greg Kwiatek (2000), 1993-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Lucio Fabro (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Victoria Sambunaris (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Fariba Hajamadi (2001), 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Victor Burgin: Nietzche's Paris (2001), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Michael Smith and Joshua White: The QuinQuag Arts and Wellness Center (2001), Archival Resource Key (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Installation, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Printed and Photographic Material, 2001-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hermann Pitz (2001), 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Luciano Fabro (2001), 1999-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Andrea Stappert: Martin Kippenberger Portraits (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Mark Dion and Morgan Puett: The Ladies Field Club of New York (2002), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Stanley Brouwn: Books (2002), 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - Richard Sharpe Shaver: Weird and Wonderful Art, Rockfogos, Paintings and Books (2002), Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Hamish Fulton: Drawings from Walks (2002), 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Allen Ruppersberg: Drawings, 1973-1980 (2002), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Harrell Fletcher: Hello There Friend (2003), 2003-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Igor and Svetlana Kopystiansky: The Day Before Tomorrow (2003), 2003-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER30
  - Igor and Svetlana Kopystiansky: The Day Before Tomorrow (2003), Digital Images, Archival Resource Key; 0.027 Gigabytes 2 computer files (Folder ER30)
  - Group Exhibition (2003), Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Victor Burgin: Room (1970) (2003), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - No One May Have This Knowledge Again (2003), 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER31
  - No One May Have This Knowledge Again (2003), Digital Documents and Archival Film Footage, Archival Resource Key; 3.396 Gigabytes 3 computer files (Folder ER31)
  - Selections from the E. Buk Collection of Technology and Invention (2004), 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Harrell Fletcher: A Moment of Doubt (2004), 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER32
  - Harrell Fletcher: A Moment of Doubt (2004), Digital Images of Artwork and Installation, 2003; Archival Resource Key; 0.015 Gigabytes 61 computer files (Folder ER32)
  - Matt Mullican and Allan McCollum: Your Fate (2004), Archival Resource Key (Box 14)
    - Concepts and Plans, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER33
    - Concepts and Plans, Digital Images, 2004; Archival Resource Key; 0.003 Gigabytes 24 computer files (Folder ER33)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2006; 2015; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 CD, Allan McCollum "The Event" (transfer not possible) (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
    - Drawings and Images (reproductions), 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Includes born-digital files, see ER34
    - Drawings and Images, Digital, 2004-2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.03 Gigabytes 164 computer files (Folder ER34)
    - Printed and Photographic Material, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Production Costs, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Sales Records, 2004-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Maria Nordman: Standing Pictures (2004), 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 published sound disc (CD) (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
  - Victoria Sambunaris (2004), 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER35
  - Victoria Sambunaris (2004), Digital Images, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.257 Gigabytes 34 computer files (Folder ER35)
  - Michael Smith and Joshua White: Take Off Your Pants (2005), 2005-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER36
  - Michael Smith and Joshua White: Take Off Your Pants (2005), Digital Images and Files, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.092 Gigabytes 22 computer files (Folder ER36)
  - Victor Burgin: Little House (2005), Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Allen Ruppersberg: Line Drawings, Book Pages, Games, and a Puzzle (2005), 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER37
  - Allen Ruppersberg: Line Drawings, Book Pages, Games, and a Puzzle (2005), Digital Images of Installation, Archival Resource Key; 0.002 Gigabytes 16 computer files (Folder ER37)
  - Twixt Two Worlds: Selections from the Collection of Ricky Jay (2005), 2004-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 17-19)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER38
  - Twixt Two Worlds: Selections from the Collection of Ricky Jay (2005), Digital Images, Audio, and Slide Presentation, 2005-2007; Archival Resource Key; 4.17 Gigabytes 404 computer files (Folder ER38)
  - Paul Etienne Lincoln: Two Mechanical Symphonies for Two Cities (2006), 2005-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER39
  - Paul Etienne Lincoln: Two Mechanical Symphonies for Two Cities (2006), Digital Images, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; 2.31 Gigabytes 52 computer files (Folder ER39)
  - Paul Etienne Lincoln: Two Mechanical Symphonies for Two Cities (2006), "Sinfonia Torinese" Installation, 2004-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER40
  - Paul Etienne Lincoln: Two Mechanical Symphonies for Two Cities (2006), "Sinfonia Torinese," Digital Images, Archival Resource Key; 0.631 Gigabytes 62 computer files (Folder ER40)
  - Matt Mullican: Three Suitcases of Truth, Love and Beauty (2006), 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 CD (transfer not possible) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER41
  - Matt Mullican: Three Suitcases of Truth, Love and Beauty (2006), Digital Images, Archival Resource Key; 0.009 Gigabytes 2 computer files (Folder ER41)
  - Michael Smith: Drawings and Videos from Storage (2007), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER42
  - Michael Smith: Drawings and Videos from Storage (2007), Digital Images and Video, 2003-2007; Archival Resource Key; 4.839 Gigabytes 23 computer files (Folder ER42)
  - Hamish Fulton: Geronimo Homeland (2007), Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Includes born-digital files, see ER43
  - Hamish Fulton: Geronimo Homeland (2007), Digital Images of Artwork and Installation, Archival Resource Key; 0.849 Gigabytes 34 computer files (Folder ER43)
  - Exhibition Files, General, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Client Files, 1983-2013; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 3.5 Linear feet Boxes 15-18
  Client files date from 1983-2013 and predominantly contain correspondence and invoices to clients. Some correspondence with institutions and galleries contain consignments and loan agreements as well.
  - 303 Gallery, 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Addison Gallery of Art, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Adler, Francis Beatty and Allen, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Alexander, Leslie (Fred Alger Management), 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - American Fine Arts Co., Colin de Land Fine Art, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Galerie Paul Andriesse, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Angle, Carol R., 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - De Appel Foundation, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Asher Faure, 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - A, General, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Josh Baer Gallery, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Bailey, Bruce, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Galerie des Beaux-Arts Galerij, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Becker, Jürgen, 1990-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - De Beir, Francis, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Belgacom Foundation, 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Berggruen, John, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Bernstein, Jill and Jay, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Beron, Edna, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Black, Marlies, 1989-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Broido, Peter, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Galerie Bruges la Morte, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Burke, William, 1986-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - B, General, 1986-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Galerie Antoine Candau, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Carre, Jean Dominique, 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Carswell, Mary, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Castleberry, May, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Chaplick, Morey, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Chenier, Robert-Jean, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Chiat, Jay, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Cohen, Eileen, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Copley, Claire, 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Cravitz, Alan, 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Cullen, Kathleen, 2003-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Cvikota, Tom, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - C, General, 1986-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Daled, Herman J., 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Danae Art International, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dannheisser, Elaine, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Dawson, David, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - DeVoy, Kiwi, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Downe, Edward R. Jr., 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Dumont-Wautier, S. A., 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Durand-Dessert, Michel, 1999-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - D, General, 1987-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - E, General, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Faerber, Katharina, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Feature Gallery, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Rosamund Felsen Gallery, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Fleiss, Marcel, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Flynn, Barbara, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - F, General, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Gershon, Dann, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Gevaert, Yves, 1989-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 19-20)
  - Gladstone, Barbara, 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Goldberg, Arthur, 1990-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
  - Goldberg, Carol, 1987-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Goldstrom, Monique and Foster, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Barbara Guggenheim Associates, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Gund, Agnes, 1992-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Gutstein, Blanche, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - G, General, 1986-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Haas, Marvin I., 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - van Haerents, Walter, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Halbreich, Kathy (Walker Art Center), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Heyman, Samuel, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Hirschl & Adler Modern, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, 2005-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Rhona Hoffman Gallery, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Hoffman-Borman Gallery, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Galerie Xavier Hufkens, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - H, General, 1986-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Jacobson, Marjory, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Johnen & Schöttle, 1987-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - J, General, 1988-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Paul Kasmin Gallery, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Kaufmann, Ruth, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Kelly, James, 2000-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kent Fine Art, 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Koeing, Walther, 1994-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kosmin, Marvin and Alice, 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - K, General, 1986-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Galerie Laage-Salomon, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Lambert, Francoise, 1989-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Landau, Emily, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Lannan Foundation, 1992-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Leiber, Steven, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Leigh, Christian, 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Lisson Gallery, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Linton, Robert, 1987-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Littman, Robert, 1986-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Lynne, Michael, 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - L, General, 1986-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - March, Philippe, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Maslow, Richard, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Maubrie, Gabrielle, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 19)